Martin P. Catherwood Library American Labor Union Constitution and Proceedings Project Files /4197
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library American Labor Union Constitution and Proceedings Project Files
1955-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
Martin P. Catherwood Library
/4197
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Case files, records (documents).
8051170
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Library
8051170
- 1994 UMI (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1993 UMI (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1992 UMI (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Copyrighted Documents/Permissions, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1990 UMI Update (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1991 UMI Update (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1989 UMI Update (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Update, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1987 Update (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1986 Upd (Box 1, Folder 10)
- UMI - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondence - Reno, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Page Estimates, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Correspondence MCA Project L, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence MCA Project M-O, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Correspondence MCA Project P-R, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Correspondence MCA Project S-V, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Additional Unions, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Supplement, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- "Lost Material", 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- TRADE/ASSOC, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Trade Assoc., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ICFTU, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- WFTU., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- WCL, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Officers' Reports, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Misc., 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Officers' Reports, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Form - Officers' Reports, Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Received - AFL - CIO, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Received - CBU, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Received - MH - IR, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Received - IU, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Received - MdBJ, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Received - M.I.T., Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Received - MiU, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Received - NYPL, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Received - NjP, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Received - NjR, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Received - DL, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Received - Wtti, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Officers Reports - Replies from Unions, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Officers Reports - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Union Newspapers, 1975-1981 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Unions, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 49-50)
- UMI Correspondence & Permissions, 1975-1994 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- UMI Listing, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 52-53)
- American Labor Unions Constitutions & Proceedings, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 54)